<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Damien LAMBLA</title>
    <link>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Damien LAMBLA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 20:53:32 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Maven deploy to OSS JFrog to Maven Central</title>
      <link>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/jfrog-bintray/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 20:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/jfrog-bintray/</guid>
      <description>Maven deploy to OSS JFrog to Maven Central JFrog BinTray Begin by creating an organisation and a package on JFrog BinTray.
Edit your package and request that your package be added to JCenter
Don&amp;rsquo;t forgot to tick the option : Host my snapshot build artifacts on the OSS Artifactory Wait for your request to be granted.
Then, Edit your profile and find your API key.
OSS JFrog Use that key as your password to connect in OSS-JFrog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUGO</title>
      <link>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/hugo/deploy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 20:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/hugo/deploy/</guid>
      <description>HUGO create a new site hugo new site me
install theme go here minimal and follow the instructions:
git submodule add https://github.com/calintat/minimal.git themes/minimal git submodule init git submodule update git submodule update --remote themes/minimal cp themes/minimal/exampleSite/config.toml  in the file config.toml set all your params, and:
baseurl = &amp;quot;http://examplesite&amp;quot; &amp;lt;- Change to https://yourgithubusername.github.io  push on your github On branch master you have the public folder (built version)
And on the hugo branch you put the hugo project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secrets and properties management</title>
      <link>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/properties-files-and-secrets-managers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 20:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/properties-files-and-secrets-managers/</guid>
      <description>Secrets and properties management Properties files with Spring boot Specify different profiles (for the different DB for example) like this in the default application.properties file:
spring.profiles.active=local  or at runtime like that:
java -Dspring.profiles.active=local -jar yourApplication.jar  It will automatically take the corresponding properties file in the classpath application-local.propertie
Secrets with Spring boot When you have to specify a secret, just define a placeholder instead:
spring.datasource.password=${db-password}  and pass the value at runtime with a Java -D variable:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some of my projects</title>
      <link>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2019 20:53:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blablanumerodeux.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Personal Website Aug 2019 – Present
Personal website / blog where I sometime post some technical articles about whatever I want to remember or to share.
This website is made with HUGO which is a static website generator made in JS.
All the articles are also available in a MarkDown format directly on my GitHub.
See project: https://lambla.eu/
Dans La Rue Homeless Jan 2019 – Present
Display a list of all the shelters available to the homeless people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>